m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影視
YYeTs.com
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
■
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com
翻譯：淫賊叫獸賽太公  受騙學生YY貓  貓中之王  醉芝士
校對：淫賊叫獸賽太公  受騙學生YY貓總監   YY貓
后期：孤帆   時間軸：YY貓
生活大爆炸
第七季  第七集
我從沒見過他這么歡樂
I've never seen him this happy before.
那是因為你從來沒有在
That's because you've never seen him
"醫藥箱補貨日"見過他
on "Restock the Medicine Cabinet Day."
你們看
Look!
新出的帶麻藥局部抗組胺劑呢
A new topical antihistamine with lidocaine.
好想趕快發疹子來用用看啊
I can't wait until I get a rash.
解脹氣藥也出了加強版呢
Oh, Gas-X has a new ultra strength.
看來他們真會看顧客意見郵箱啊
I guess they really do read their mail.
那不是質子教授嗎
Hey, isn't that Professor Proton?
是啊
Oh, yeah.
你們看他  像普通人一樣排隊
Look at him, just standing in line
好像自己30年前并不是個二流名人似地
like he wasn't moderately famous 30 years ago.
去跟他打招呼吧
Let's go say hello.
我們還是別煩人家比較好吧
Oh, maybe we shouldn't bother him.
我沒有要去煩他啊  我是要去跟他聊聊
I'm not going to bother him, I'm going to talk to him.
他總以為這兩者不一樣
He thinks there's a difference.
亞瑟
Arthur?
亞瑟  是我啊
Arthur, it's me--
謝爾頓·庫珀
Sheldon Cooper.
你可能因為年事已高忘了我是誰了
You may not remember because of your advanced age.
相信我  你化成灰我也認得
Trust me, I... I remember.
這位是我的女朋友  艾米
This is my girlfriend, Amy.
艾米  這位是電視圈傳奇亞瑟·杰弗里斯
Amy, this is television legend Arthur Jeffries.
他的科普節目啟發了無數孩子
His science show inspired millions of children.
等  等等
Ho-hold on.
你...  你有女朋友啊
You... You have a girlfriend?
是的  久仰大名啊
Yes, and I've heard so much about you.
而且你看  我們穿著同款矯正鞋呢
Hey look-- we're wearing the same orthopedic shoes.
真不敢相信我跟名人穿同樣的鞋
I can't believe I dress like a celebrity.
現在我明白了
O-Okay, I get it now.
你好  我是萊納德·霍夫斯塔德
Dr. Jeffries, hello again. Leonard Hofstadter.
是你啊  我記得你的女朋友
Oh, oh, right, I remember your-your girlfriend.
她...  她在嗎
Is-Is she... is she here?
她不在這里
No, she's not.
你是來補什么藥的存貨呢
So, what prescription are you getting filled?
-謝爾頓  -別說  讓我猜猜
- Sheldon. - Wait, I want to guess.
別告訴我答案
Don't tell me.
我本來就沒打算告訴你
I wasn't going to tell you.
謝爾頓  別玩了
Sheldon, come on.
不不不  玩這個我最拿手了
No, no, no. I'm really good at this.
好  給我的提示
All right, give me a hint.
是不是跟排某些液體有困難有關
Does it involve difficulty initiating a stream of anything?
看我的年紀就知道  猜中很容易吧
Well, given my age, that's more than just a lucky guess.
謝爾頓  我們還是去取笑
Hey, Sheldon, let's go mock the people
買順勢療法藥的人吧  你不是很喜歡嗎
buying homeopathic medicine-- you love that.
但是我現在跟朋友一起
But I'm hanging out with my friend,
我們聊得正歡呢
and we're having fun.
你看他多開心
Look how happy he is.
妮妮這周五要在家里辦閨蜜之夜
Bernie's having a girls' night on Friday at our place.
不如那晚咱倆出去玩呀
You want to do something?
-那晚我有事呢  -什么事
- Actually, I'm busy. - Doing what?
科羅拉多大街那邊開了一家新體育酒吧...
There's a new sports bar over on Colorado Ave...
-你也要去參加閨蜜之夜  -是啦
- You're going to girls' night. - Yeah.
你知道她們是要串珠寶的對吧
You know they're making jewelry, right?
你以為那主意是她們想出來的嗎
You think they came up with that?
她們本來是要喝啤酒  射飛鏢好嗎
They were going to drink beer and play darts.
怎么樣啦[什么上升]
What's up?
絕對不是他的睪丸酮水平
Not his testosterone levels.
別亂說
Excuse me.
人家對自己的男子氣概很滿意好咩
I happen to be very comfortable with my masculinity.
這怎么可能
How is that possible?
質子教授給我發了電郵
Hey, I got an email from Professor Proton.
好耶  他說什么了
Goody! What's it say?
他在寫一篇納米真空管的論文
He's working on a paper about nano vacuum tubes,
問我能不能幫他看看
and wants to know if I'd take a look at it.
奇怪
That's strange.
他居然會找你  而不是找我幫忙
That he would come to you for that and not me.
我收到他兩封電郵呢
Oh, I got two emails from him.
"你有萊納德的郵箱嗎"
"Do you have Leonard's email address?"
還有
And...
"不用了  我找到了"
"Never mind, I found it."
他居然會選你不選我
I can't believe he picked you over me.
你也不會想看一篇好幾十年沒正經
You don't want to read a paper by some old has-been
搞過科研的過氣老頭寫的論文呢
who hasn't done any real science in decades.
這有什么好哭訴的
Yeah, it's nothing to cry about.
謝爾頓·庫伯才不哭呢
Sheldon Cooper does not cry.
有道理  你個機器人碰水會生
It's true, you'd rust.
想到我居然曾經當他是我偶像
And to think I idolized that man.
我何苦呢
And why?
說到底  他不過也是個好萊塢偽君子罷了
At the end of the day he's just another Hollywood phony.
這事情真的值得你不開心嗎
Is it really worth getting upset about?
常言道  別見你心中的英雄
They say don't meet your heroes.
不要窺探他們名望與名聲背后的真實
Don't peek behind that curtain of fame and celebrity,
如果你犯了這禁忌  你會看到真實的他們
because if you do, you'll see them as they really are--
墮落的賣笑戲子
degenerate carnival folk.
別這樣  他只是個退休的兒童節目主持
Come on, he's a retired kids show host.
這才更糟呢
That's even worse.
用美好的科學當糖果
Using the sweet candy of science
騙取小孩對他的愛慕
to trick children into loving him.
死淫賊
Pervert.
你有仔細想過
Have you ever thought about
為什么亞瑟沒找你讀論文嗎
why Arthur didn't want you to read his paper?
我想過
Yes, I have.
我唯一的結論就是
And my only conclusion
他那天在藥房買的藥
is the prescription he was picking up the other day
是要治神經病的
was for cuckoo pills.
有可能是他覺得你有點過了吧
Maybe he found you, um, a bit much.
你這話說得才過吧
That's kind of a stretch.
要說社交技巧
Look, when it comes to social skills,
我已經掌握了三大技巧
I've mastered the big three.
首先是靦腆一笑
There's the coy smile.
以及友善的輕笑
There's the friendly chuckle.
以及如何發出同情音
There's the vocalization of sympathy.
最后這個太難了  我還在練
That last one's tricky, I'm still working on it.
就我那天看到的情況來看
From what I saw the other day,
我能理解他或...
I could understand why he and...
有些人可能會覺得你
some people might find you...
什么
What?
算了
Doesn't matter.
不行  快說
No, go ahead, say it.
我知道你想說什么
I know what it is.
我這輩子聽過無數遍了
I've heard it my whole life.
你想說的是"惹人厭"
The word's "annoying".
說吧  說吧
Go ahead, say it.
快說  說我惹人厭
Say it. Say I'm annoying.
謝爾頓
Sheldon...
我才不會覺得受傷
Oh, it won't hurt my feelings.
說吧  艾米  說我惹人厭啊
Go ahead, Amy, say I'm annoying.
我惹人厭  我超級惹人厭
I'm annoying. I'm annoying.
我最惹人厭了  沒錯
I'm annoying. Yeah, now, uh...
你要去哪里
Now where are you going?
你知道你想說出口  快說啊
Look, you know you want to say it-- say it.
說我惹人厭  快說啊
Say I'm annoying. Go ahead, say it.
說啊  艾米  快說啊
Say it. Say it. Amy, say it.
這妞不能忍受我是對的就走啊
Well, she can't stand it when I'm right.
真有意思
This is fun.
我會像戴著珠寶的那種傲嬌的貴婦
I'm going to feel like such a vixen wearing jewelry
只不過我不會對一大堆藥物過敏
that doesn't have a list of medications I'm allergic to.
佩妮  你做得怎么樣
Penny, how's it going over there?
很好  只是我有點搞不定膠水
Good-- I'm just having little trouble with the glue.
你難道不會用膠水嗎
How do you not know how to use glue?
你學前班老逃課了吧
Did you ditch pre-school?
是啊  當時我忙著跟二年級的學生約會呢
Yeah, but only because I was dating a second grader.
各位好啊
Hello, everyone.
好吧  你想說什么就說吧
Okay, let me have it.
你只管開"拉杰是娘們"的玩笑好了
Let's hear all the "Raj is a girl" jokes.
你想錯了
Nope.
伯納黛特說這樣不對  她不許我這樣
Bernadette told me it isn't nice and I'm not allowed.
那還真是多謝了
Thank you.
所以我不會嘲笑你
So I won't be making fun of you,
也不會恥笑你喜歡的事物
or the things you like,
更不會譏笑你"只想玩樂"的事實
or the fact that you just want to have fun.
源自辛迪·勞帕的著名單曲《Girls Just Wanna Have Fun 女孩們只想玩樂》
華仔  別說了
Howie, stop.
過來看看我做的東西
Come on, look at what I'm making.
還挺好看的嘛
Oh, that's actually pretty nice.
我在做手鐲
I'm making a bracelet.
而我做的是"一團糟"
Yeah, I'm just making a mess.
你們其實可以拿我的焊鐵玩
You know, instead of beads and glue,
而不是在這光玩珠子和膠水
you guys can use my soldering iron.
這樣你們可以做更酷的東西
You'd be able to make much cooler stuff.
我覺得這樣就挺好  謝啦
Oh, I think we're doing just fine, thank you.
-老實說  我想試試  -我也是
- Actually, I'd kind of like to try that. - Me, too.
馬上給你們拿來
Be right back.
我胳膊上怎么黏有開心果
When did I have pistachios?
亞瑟
Arthur.
門環
Door knocker.
從那個電視節目賺的吧
That's TV money.
同名DIY電視節目
謝爾頓  你來這兒干嘛
Sheldon, what are you doing here?
抱歉  我吵醒你了嗎
I'm sorry, did I wake you?
當然啦  現在都晚上7點半了
Of course you woke me, it's 7:30.
本來我可以早點到的
Well, I would have been here sooner,
但不知道為什么
but for some reason your home
你家不在"好萊塢明星之家"這幅地圖上
isn't on this map of Hollywood stars.
你找我有事嗎  謝爾頓
What do you want, Sheldon?
我的女朋友指出
It's been pointed out by my girlfriend
那天我可能惹到你了
that I may have been annoying to you.
這么懂事的姑娘你可別放手
She sounds like a keeper.
總之我想跟你道歉
Anyway, I wanted to apologize.
真的很對不起
I am truly sorry.
好的  我接受你的道歉  晚安
All right, apology accepted. Have a nice night.
不  還有呢  既然我們冰釋前嫌
No, no, now that... we've cleared the air,
我還想跟你商量一件事
I wanted to discuss another matter with you.
謝爾頓  再過兩個小時  我就得起床
Sheldon, in a couple hours, I have to get up,
尿個尿  然后在房子里游蕩[夢游]
pee and then wander around the house.
那我長話短說
Well, then, I'll make this quick.
我想跟你談談你發給萊納德那篇論文
Um, I want to talk about the paper you sent Leonard.
我知道他說可行性很高
Now, I know he said it's promising
他也打算跟你合作
and he's going to collaborate on it,
但現在我們又是朋友了
but now that you and I are friends again,
我隨時聽候您差遣
I am at your disposal.
坦白說  借助我的名字和聲望會對論文大有幫助
Frankly, lending my name and reputation to it will help,
因為很多人都認為你已經是"過氣的前浪"
because a lot of people think that you're a washed-up has-been.
或已經"死在沙灘上"了
Or dead.
那我真是走了大運啊
I should be so lucky.
那你覺得怎么樣
So, uh, what do you say?
如果你還是跟以前一樣
You know, if it's all the same with you,
那我還是繼續跟萊納德合作吧
I think I'll stick with Leonard.
因為我惹人厭  對吧
It's because I'm annoying, right?
我知道  說啊
I know it is. Say it.
快說  說我惹人厭
Say it. Say I'm annoying.
-晚安  -說啊
- Good night. - Say it.
亞瑟  說啊  說我惹人厭
Arthur, say it. Say I'm annoying.
說啊  快說啊
Say it. Say it.
說我惹人厭
I'm annoying. Say it.
你超級惹人厭
You're annoying!
人家好傷心啊
Wow, that really hurt.
如果在我小時候  有人跟我說
If you would have told me when I was a kid
我長大后會有機會
that someday I would be doing science
跟質子教授一起做實驗
next to Professor Proton,
我一定不會相信
I would not have believed you.
如果有人跟我說
If someone had told me
人們在我83歲的時候
that people would still call me Professor Proton
還會稱我為"質子教授"
when I was 83 years old,
我肯定不會戒煙
I never would have quit smoking.
抱歉  杰弗里斯博士  我只是太興奮了
I'm sorry, Dr. Jeffries, I'm just excited.
你對于納米真空管的想法很有意思
This nano vacuum tube idea of yours is really interesting.
你好啊  萊納德
Hello, Leonard.
你好  亞瑟
Oh, hello, Arthur.
你們倆都在這里  真是意外的巧合呀
What an odd coincidence that you're both here.
有什么巧合的
Why is it odd?
因為碰巧的是  我今天也跟一位
Because as it just so happens, I'm also spending the day
深受兒童喜愛的電視科學明星在一起
with a beloved children's television science personality.
對不對呀  我的新友兼新同事
Isn't that right, new friend and colleague,
美國科教節目《比爾·奈教科學》主持人
教科學的比爾·奈
Bill Nye the Science Guy.
不好意思  我用新型號替換了你
Sorry, I replaced you with a newer model.
亞瑟·杰弗里斯
Wow, Arthur Jeffries.
見到您真是太榮幸了
It's an honor to meet you.
沒有您的鋪墊  也不會有我的節目
My show never would have happened without yours.
所以我跟我律師說你是抄襲我
That's what I told my lawyers.
奈先生  你好
Mr. Nye, hello.
被他把你卷進這無謂的紛爭里  真是抱歉
I'm sorry he got you involved in this nonsense.
他說是請我來給學生上課的
He said I'd be speaking to a class.
不對  我是說請你來給某人上一課[教訓]
No, I said you were teaching someone a lesson.
好了  走吧
Now let's go.
你們在研究什么呢
What are you guys working on?
我們在研制納米真空管
Oh, uh, we're making nano vacuum tubes.
很有意思嘛
That's interesting.
你從我這里偷的哽還不夠嗎
Haven't you stolen enough from me?
走開啦  領結男
Back off, bow tie!
各位
Hey, guys...
這一副怎么樣
What do you think?
佩妮  做得真漂亮
Wow, Penny, good job.
謝了  在商場買的  4塊99
Thanks. Target, $4.99.
我再去倒一杯酒
I'm getting a drink.
你在做什么呢
What are you working on?
幫我媽做一串項鏈
Oh, I'm making a necklace for my mom.
真孝順
That's sweet.
最近她和我爸的
Yeah, she and my dad are going through
關系有點緊張
a bit of a rough patch, so
所以我想表示一下讓她知道
I wanted to do something to let her know
我掛念著她
I was thinking about her.
他們干嘛吵架呢
What's going on with them?
他們有點小小的溝通不良
They're just having a little trouble communicating.
我爸說我媽的聲音
My dad says it's because the sound of my mom's voice
讓他想把自己耳朵揪下來
makes him want to tear his ears off
再縫在他的眼睛上
and sew them over his eyes
這樣他就永遠不用再看見她了
so he never has to look at her again.
嗨
Hi.
-大家好啊  -嗨
- Hey, guys. - Hello.
看看是誰把
Look who's here to put
猶太和珠寶音似
"猶太人"帶進"珠寶之夜"了
the "Jew" In "Jewelry Night"!
種族笑話你自己說就沒關系是吧
Oh, sure, so it's fine when you say it.
抱歉我們遲到了
Sorry we're late.
我順便去了實驗室
I wanted to swing by the lab
把更給力的工具給搬來了
and pick up some even cooler tools for us to use.
我沒想到你居然又出現了
I didn't know you were coming again.
上周還挺好玩的
Well, last week was a blast.
再說  我想你們也愿意有個男士陪伴吧
Plus, I thought you might like having a guy here.
其實一點也不好笑
It was not funny.
那你帶了什么工具來
So, what tools did you bring?
各種制作珠寶模子的工具
Everything we need to make jewelry molds.
銀  坩堝
Here's some silver, a crucible
還有用來融化的乙炔炬
and an acetylene torch to melt it down.
這個看起來有意思
Ooh, that looks like fun.
還是等你先搞定膠水
Maybe you should master glue
再學習玩火吧
before you move on to fire.
好了  誰想先玩啊
Okay, who's up first?
拉杰什  你想再做一副和那項鏈
Rajesh, do you want to make a bracelet for your mom
搭配的手鐲送給你媽嗎
to go with the necklace?
不用了
No, thanks.
我也想給我媽做一串項鏈
I was gonna make a necklace for my mom,
可惜  她胖得脖子都沒有
but unfortunately, she doesn't have a neck.
她下巴之下是脂肪  脂肪之下就是腳
She's just chins and fat and feet.
好  我們馬上就可以開始了
Okay, we're almost ready to go.
把線連上  就可以開始測試這些管子了
Once we bond the wires, we can test the tubes.
太讓人激動了  我覺得
This is so exciting, I-I feel...
就像重新回到75歲一樣
like I'm 75 again.
老天爺
Oh, God.
出...什么事了
What... what is it?
謝爾頓發了一張
Sheldon just sent me a picture
他和比爾·奈一起喝冰沙的照片
of him and Bill Nye getting smoothies.
我  我能問個問題嗎
Can-can I ask you a question?
當然  問吧
Yeah, sure.
你怎么能忍受謝爾頓這種人啊
W-Why do you put up with Sheldon?
因為我們是朋友呀
Oh, uh, you know, because we're friends.
為什么呀
Why?
-你真喜歡給人出難題  -當然
- Wow, you ask really hard questions. - Yeah.
我知道他總是惹人厭
Look, I-I know he can be aggravating,
但你要知道
but what you have to remember is that
他不是故意的
he's not doing it on purpose.
只是他這人天性如此
It's just how he is.
其實他很忠誠也很可靠
But he's also loyal and trustworthy
我們在一起挺開心的
and we have fun together...
你...你知道自己是在描述一只狗吧
You... you know you're describing a dog.
他的確咬過我一次
He did bite me once.
但他解釋說
But in his defense,
我在他進食時突然從背后冒出來  所以
I came up behind him while he was eating, so...
狗都不喜歡那樣
Yeah, they-they hate that.
謝爾頓是我遇見過的最聰明的家伙
You know what, Sheldon is the smartest person I have ever met.
他并不是完人  所以才需要我
And he's a little broken and he needs me.
我大概也需要他吧
I guess I need him, too.
為  為什么呢
Why-why is that?
你非得打破沙鍋問到底  是吧
Boy, you will not let this go, will you?
我的天
Oh, geez.
又是謝爾頓發來的照片嗎
Another photo from Sheldon?
不是  我得去接他一下
No, I have to go pick him up.
比爾·奈把他拋棄在冰沙店了
Bill Nye ditched him at the smoothie place.
大概把他的錢包也順手偷走了
He probably stole his wallet, too.
如果你們感興趣的話
You know, if you guys are interested,
有種技術可以讓我把你們的一束頭發
there's a technique where I can take a lock of your hair,
提煉成碳粉
refine it into carbon dust,
然后用實驗室的液壓器
and use the hydraulic press at work
把它轉變成一顆小小的鉆石
to turn it into a tiny little diamond
里面還有你自己的DNA哦
with your DNA in it.
太神奇了吧
Oh, that's amazing!
看到妮妮訂婚戒指了嗎
Yeah. See Bernie's engagement ring?
原料是我媽背部的體毛
That came right off my mom's back.
他開玩笑的
He's kidding.
真是這樣  鉆石會大得多
If that were true, it'd be so much bigger.
我叫霍華德
"My name is Howard.
我可以把你的毛發變成鉆石
I can make your hair into diamonds.
我媽有病態肥胖癥
My mom is morbidly obese.
人人都愛我
Everybody love me."
為啥一股很不爽我的口氣
Whoa, where is that coming from?
我告訴你為什么
I'll tell you where it's coming from.
你之前嘲笑我參加閨蜜之夜
All you do is make fun of me for coming to girls' night
現在你又跑來這里毀了大家的好時光
and now you're here ruining it for everyone.
拉杰  淡定
Raj, cool it...
他要給咱們做鉆石呢
he's gonna make us hair diamonds.
我怎么毀了你們的好時光
How am I ruining anything?
我只是想幫你把珠寶做得更好
I'm just trying to help you make better jewelry.
但是重點不在珠寶
But this isn't about the jewelry.
而在于在這里
This is about me having a place
我可以敞開心扉  無所不談
where I can open up about my feelings.
你什么時候開始不能對我敞開心扉談了
Since when can't you open up with me?
有些話題
There are just some things
我覺得和姑娘們說更自在
that I feel more comfortable sharing with the girls,
因為她們不會嘲笑我
because they won't make fun of me
不會給我取綽號  或是問我
or and call me names, or ask me if my
庫薩帕里你的內褲是不是卷在了一起
"Koothrapanties are in a bunch."
意為因為小事就發脾氣
兄弟  我那是開玩笑的
Buddy, I was just joking around.
有時候你的玩笑很傷人
Yeah, well, sometimes your jokes hurt.
你說得對
Well, you're right.
我沒意識到會讓你有這種感受
I didn't realize I was making you feel that way.
你能坦白告訴我真是太勇敢了
It was very brave of you to tell me.
謝謝
Thank you.
對我來說不容易
It wasn't easy.
他們會搶在我和謝爾頓之前先上床
They're gonna have sex before Sheldon and I do,
我就知道
I know it.
亞瑟
Arthur.
你好  謝爾頓
Hi, Sheldon.
真意外在這里看見你
I'm surprised to see you here.
我也意外
Yeah, me, too.
我爬到三樓時
Somewhere around the third floor,
我眼前都開始出現白光了[回光返照]
I began to see a white light.
我去叫萊納德
I'll get Leonard.
不用  我...
No, no, no, I'm...
我是來找你的
I'm here... I'm here to see you.
如果你想通過我的關系找比爾·奈
If you're hoping to get in touch with Bill Nye,
我幫不了你
I can't help you.
我已經被通知他現在是
I've been informed that he's now
限制令男比爾·奈
Bill Nye the Restraining Order Guy.
不是  我...
No, I'm...
我想  如果不太麻煩的話
I-I was thinking, if it isn't too much trouble,
我希望你給我的論文提提意見
I'd like to get your opinion about my-my paper.
謝謝
Thank you.
這是我的榮幸
It would be an honor.
太好了
Oh. Uh, great.
其實你可以不用給我稿子了
Well, actually, I don't need that.
我已經黑進你的郵箱看過了
I hacked into your e-mail account and read it.
那你覺得如何
And... what did you think?
首先  我覺得
Well, first, I think the fact that
你使用生日作為郵箱密碼
you use your birthday as a password
這個錯誤太丟人
is embarrassing.
多謝提醒
Thank you.
第二
Second, um...
我覺得你的論文極具啟發性
I thought your paper was inspired.
你的肯定對我來說意義重大
Oh, well, that... that means a lot to me.
進來喝杯茶好嗎
Can I invite you in for tea?
不用了  我真的得...
Uh, no, no. I-I really...
我得走了
I have... I have to run.
亞瑟  你好嗎
Hey, Arthur. How are you?
喝一杯也無妨
Well, I guess one cup wouldn't hurt.
兄弟  什么事
Oh, hey, buddy, what's up?
我為自己那天晚上的表現感到內疚
Well, I was feeling bad about how I acted the other night
所以我給你做了個小禮物
so I made you a little something.
這么客氣干嘛呀
You didn't have to do that.
很有趣
Well, it was fun.
我運用了你教我們的珠寶制作技藝
I used some of the jewelry techniques you taught us.
這是一個光劍皮帶扣
It's a lightsaber belt buckle.
太厲害了  謝謝
Wow, this is so cool, thanks.
好戲在后頭
Oh gets better.
更精彩的好戲還在后面  瞧
And that's not even the best part. See?
我也有一個
I have one, too.
你瞧
Check it out.
你可以戴上你的  咱們隨時可以來一場
You can wear yours and we can have little sword fights
激情小劍大比拼
whenever we want.
質子教授節目  我心中排名第八的那集是
Yeah, and my eighth favorite episode of Professor Proton
泡騰劑式消化片火箭
was "Alka-Seltzer Rocket."
你說  撲通撲通  嘶嘶嘶嘶
You said, "Plop, plop, fizz, fizz,
精彩的發射來一次
oh, what a blast-off it is."
記得嗎  記得這集嗎
Remember? Remember that?
記得嗎
Remember?
他就是這德行  就是這樣
He can't help it. He can't.
他真的沒辦法
He really can't.
你等著
You wait here.
我去拿些消化片
I'll get some Alka-Seltzer,
我們可以造出火箭
we can build that rocket,
然后朝著比爾·奈家發射
and we can shoot it at Bill Nye's house.
只要我離他超過五百英尺范圍就行
As long as I'm not within 500 feet of it.
那么   你...
So, you, uh...
你有沒有
you have... you have any...
單身的奶奶或外婆
single grandmothers?
-抱歉  兩位都嫁人了  -很好
- Sorry, they're both married. - Good.
婚姻幸福嗎
H-Happily?